{
    "id": "416b4c24bbf14d30aeb84da3695a5390",
    "title": "I’d Rather, I Wish, I’d Better",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0d604c41dbb443dc8992dfb328dd25fa",
            "title": "I'd Rather, Had Better, I Wish",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I would rather you ........................... on Monday.",
                    "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't come",
                        "didn't come",
                        "wouldn't come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I'd rather you .................................. fight with me in public.",
                    "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't",
                        "didn't",
                        "wouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You'd better ............................. now before he gets angry.",
                    "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "to leave",
                        "left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I 'd rather you ............................. me with the housework.",
                    "description": "After would rather we use a past tense to refer to the present or future.",
                    "answers": [
                        "help",
                        "helped",
                        "had helped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You'd better .................................. smoking.",
                    "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "stop",
                        "stopped",
                        "to stop"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We'd better ................................... seats.",
                    "description": "After had better we use the infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "reserve",
                        "to reserve",
                        "reserved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ............................... there when they arrived.",
                    "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "had been",
                        "will be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ............................... like that.",
                    "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't behave",
                        "hadn't behaved",
                        "don't behave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I .................................. out of school at",
                    "description": "We use a past perfect tense after wish to talk about the past.",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't drop",
                        "wouldn't drop",
                        "hadn't dropped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ................................... handsome.",
                    "description": "We use a past tense after I wish with present or future meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "have been",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish that it ………………………….. stop raining soon.",
                    "description": "We use a past tense after I wish with present or future meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish dad ……………………… come soon.",
                    "description": "We use would after wish to express our impatience or dissatisfaction with something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}